{"_id": "b1845713", "question": "Which is the best doctor for treating and managing stroke and stroke rehabilitation?", "answers": "For treating acute stroke survivors(less than 3 months), best to have a neurologist to ensure chances of second stroke are minimized, also to assess damage to the brain, assess further risk and complications, and prescribe the necessary medicationss. For rehabilitation, see a rehab doctor who will develop the therapy program for therapists to follow."}
{"_id": "ce29afd8", "question": "Which is the best doctor for treating and managing stroke and stroke rehabilitation in Gurgaon?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "76c0a1ff", "question": "How would I start to manage a stroke?", "answers": "Stroke can be treated expertly ,diagnose proper reason of stroke it might be diabetic blockage,clot of blood, thickened artery etc. Try to remove the basic cause so that supply of blood to the brain can be normal..proper exercise is must for defected part of the body. Maintain the blood pressure. Relax the patient mentally."}
{"_id": "893040fd", "question": "How do you cure a hemorrhagic stroke?", "answers": "A hemorrhagic stroke is not “cured”. The blood that leaks into the brain is fatal to cells that come in contact with it. I have a permanent legion deep in my brain.\nWhen hemorrhagic stroke is diagnosed, the patient is stabilized and closely monitored (hourly neuro checks, 7x24). If the bleeding doesn’t stop, they may have to operate, but my bleeding resolved on its own. I was in ICU for about six days, then was transferred to an acute care rehab hospital where I spent about six weeks learning how to take care of myself, how to walk, and how to deal with other deficits.\nI’m still doing my physical and occupational therapy exercises after more than two years. When I sit or lie around and don’t do my exercises, my deficits become more pronounced. I installed a ballet barre in my study, for me to use when needed for balance. Before, I was exercising in the kitchen, using the counter for balance. Every time I walk by the barre, I try to do something. Pushups, tricep dips, single leg squats, etc. It adds up.\nRecovery from stroke can last the rest of one’s life. It only stops when the stroke survivor stops trying."}
{"_id": "de87de80", "question": "Cricket (sport): How has Younis khan managed to score 9000 plus test runs with such limited range of strokes?", "answers": "Younis Khan lost his two brothers to heart attacks, one in Germany and one in Ukraine, and was left stunned when his sister died in Mardan. His father also died around the same time. Mid last year, he lost his nephew while he was in Sri Lanka which forced him to quit the tour and make an early return home. I doubt if anyone, struck by so many tragic deaths in the family within a span of six years, can carry on with both life and cricket with such a big heart. He is the only player to score test centuries in 11 countries after Rahul Dravid who has actually scored in 10 countries and the only Pakistani player who carries a record of reaching 10000+ runs in his career.\nRetirement only means that it is the time for a new adventure. May god bless you with lot of happiness and good health. Happy retirement, you legend."}
{"_id": "6a831daa", "question": "How do I manage the extreme fatigue 14 months post-stroke?", "answers": "It’s best to talk with your doctor about fatigue. It could be that the medications are too strong and doses need to be readjusted (heart medications are tiring in itself). So s/he can see if adjusting the dose or using another medication maybe right for you.\nAnother problem can be getting RESTFUL sleep. I still have that problem after my stroke where I can’t sleep for like 8hrs at once. I sleep for like 4hrs and wake up like clockwork, like the internal sleep clock got fried after the stroke. So sleeping for 4hrs and taking a nap doesn’t feel restful. Make a sleep diary and write down when you went to bed and got up and any naps you took in between. Bring that to your doctor, too.\nAfter a stroke pathways get damaged. It just takes one to ruin getting restful sleep. Mid-brain strokes are plagued with sleep disorders.\nIf it’s a sleeping disorder, they also may want to recheck your breathing for sleep apnea, too. For months after my stroke I would wake up suddenly as I couldn’t breathe well. Took a good year for that to pass.\nDepression/anxiety is also so common after stroke, the docs write a prescription by default even. There’s good reason for it, as the depression/anxiety can last for a long time. Again all it takes is a damaged pathway. It’s nothing to be ashamed of, your body went through grueling stress, and it can only take so much.\nSo the next time when you visit your doctor, have a talk about those issues. Give him/her your sleep log, too. That way the doc can SEE what’s going on, and if necessary to refer you to a specialist."}
{"_id": "dd2f18fc", "question": "What happens when we stroke a key on a keyboard? Does the character that the keyboard gives get directly written to stdin, or is there any buffer between the device and stdin? How does the kernel manage this?", "answers": "The keyboard doesn’t send characters, it sends scancodes. It’s the job of the OS to translate those to characters if needed, using the currently-selected keyboard layout options (which in Windows are per-app).\nOtherwise there are probably buffers at the interrupt request level, then buffers at the input stream level and what not. For example you might notice when your computer is starting to hang (the OS, not just an app), the reaction is different than when an app hangs - press enough keys, and your PC speaker will start beeping (probably indicating the kernel-level buffer is exhausted).\nAnd it’s easy to see that it’s not directly to stdin by the fact that this leaves the question of which stdin unanswered - every process has its own, and depending on where you alt-tab, the keys will get routed to a different process."}
{"_id": "ff399f53", "question": "What are the best pain management methods for post-stroke headaches/migraines?", "answers": "First, it depends on whether they are headaches or migraines. They are physiologically two different conditions with different causes and symptoms. The only thing in common between a headache and a migraine is that they both involve head pain. Migraine is not a synonym for “very bad headache.” How you treat a headache and how you treat or prevent a migraine are also very different. So, unless you clarify whether you intended to ask about post-stroke headaches or post-stroke migraine, the only answers you’ll get are people who don’t know they’re different… and that’s probably not the best source of information.\nHeadaches are usually treated with various different types of analgesics, ranging from over the counter NSAIDs or headache specific meds like Extra-Strength Excedrin to prescription NSAIDs. Even with OTC meds, talk to your care provider because even OTC meds can have life-threatening side effects, interfere with other meds your on, and create bleeding issues which could be catastrophic post stroke.\nMigraines are treated by one of two types of therapies - preventative (prophylactic) or at the time of an attack (abortive). Prophylactic therapies include meds like beta blockers, calcium channel blockers, anti-depressants, anti seizure meds, CGRPs, Botox injections, or non-traditional therapies like massage, physical therapy, acupuncture, etc. Abortives include symptom treating meds like anti emetics, DHE, triptans, opioids, etc (Ignore the individual who said opioids cannot be used to treat migraine. It shouldn’t be the first choice, nor should they be for anything, but for stroke patients who cannot take DHE, triptans, and/or other allergies and therapeutic failures, they are viable options when properly monitored and do help many migraineurs). There are also surgical options like a nerve stimulator implant and some other choices, but those are after meds have failed\nYou cannot get a specific treatment off Quora or any other place on the internet. Not only have you not specified whether they’re headaches or migraines, as I mentioned. But, also there are many significant medical history factors, potential meds, other underlying medical issues, etc which will factor into safe therapy choices. Talk to your neurologist for the best option given your specific situation"}
{"_id": "97ff75ab", "question": "What are the possible management of stroke/paralysis in Ayurveda?", "answers": "Stroke or the so called Cerebro Vascular Accidents can manifest due to many causes. Can be cerebral thrombosis, hemorrhage, embolism, tumors etc. When a sroke is suspected (stroke in evolution), rush the patient to a tertiary care level hospital with a stroke unit with specialist care providers. Investigate, monitir and decide the interventions according to the findings. Al these are not possible at all in any ayurveda hospitals. Hence the first line management is better done in that sort of a setting\nWhen the patient is stabilized and is discharged with a prescription and physitherapy advices as the case maybe, proceed with that. You will generally get an advice for review after 3 or 4 weeks. Well, do that. By the time, the patient must have improved on various pointers.\nThere come sthe definite scope of neuro-rehabilitation in deserving cases. Ayurveda does that with an edge over any other interventions available."}
{"_id": "9ba290ee", "question": "How do I answer why I have not had an employer for three years because I've been healing from a major trauma and stroke? I have over 20 years experience as a litigation paralegal/office manager.", "answers": "You respond with a business reason for your gap;\n“Due to a personal issue, it was best for me to focus on resolving the issue. I am happy to share that the issue is behind me and I am prepared to use my experience to be a productive employee. Segue into your spectacular elevator speech and Wow them with your accomplishments.”\nIf you have gotten an interview then your resume is clear about your capabilities. Use the time to talk about your potential fit with this employer. Focus on what you are bringing to the workplace.\nThe employer wants to know you won’t flake out and leave as you did previously. They don’t really want to know what prevented you from working if it’s in the past. Never mention the word “major trauma” in a workplace setting, even after getting the job. If you haven’t gotten your mental health in order, save those words and subsequent discussions for a licensed therapist."}
{"_id": "0840dd0f", "question": "I want to link my mobile number to my Aadhar. But could not manage to get an appointment online. It's always showing all slots booked within a fraction of second at the stroke of midnight. How will I get the appointment?", "answers": "Go for nearest eSeva offices in person and tell them that you want to link number and they will tell you to wait or leave if they are busy with appointments. If they told you to wait then no issues your work will be done and if they tell you to leave then in polite manner ask them its really important and you will wait if its possible for them to squeeze your work in between their appointments and if that works then well and good if not raise a complaint regarding online services and eSeva services.\nI hope your work gets done in time\nHope you found the Answer.\nThank You,\nHave a Great Day 🖖\nJai Hind!"}
{"_id": "114da3e7", "question": "Has anyone ever been blocked on 8 Ball Pool for transferring money?", "answers": "Yes,, two of my friends were blocked while they were transferring coins to each other. Once blocked u can't play with the same account again. Now 8 ball pool has a limit of games to be played against friends,now u can't transfer more than 50000. Earlier it was unlimited.."}
{"_id": "4dbce18f", "question": "Can you tell me which way is best to get into the Heritage Institute of Technology through management quota and at the most reasonable price?", "answers": "Please contact Heritage Institute of Technology reception personally by going there and you will be guided to the right people"}
{"_id": "f60396cc", "question": "Have you had a stroke? Did you manage to recover?", "answers": "Well I guess I did. I was in the hospital for something else, so the Dr wanted a cat scan. When I was feeling better the Dr came to talk to me and he told me that the cat scan showed that I had 3 Tia's. That means I had 3 mini strokes. He ask me if I can remember any problems. So he referred me to a neurologist. The neurologist wanted to send me for more tests. One ofthemisa MRI. Well that didn't go well cuz I am extremely costraphobic. So I never took that test. I also never went back to see him. He was very rude to me and a complete butt hole! I haven't had any symptoms and it's been over a year. I am counting my many blessings that it does not rear it's ugly face."}
{"_id": "0accc316", "question": "My hamster died because the apartment’s AC stopped working and he had a heat stroke. Do I get something from the apartment management or is it just “Oh well your hamster couldn’t survive 80 degrees.”?", "answers": "You could try to bring a lawsuit against them, but unfortunately the system protects property owners pretty well in this sort of situation. Most don't understand how much pets really mean to some people. It's probably best for you to grieve your loss and move on. A/C is considered a “luxury item\" and is not even required in Rental units. Even in States that get extremely hot, like Southern Utah. You would be surprised how many elderly and disabled people die every year from not having a cooling system in their homes."}
{"_id": "efcb2d49", "question": "How does Proust manage to spend 1,100 pages to describe 2 or 3 social dinner parties? Is that a stroke of genius or overkill?", "answers": "I think the hundred page Overture to Swann's Way is the greatest prose passage in all literature. And beginning with À L'Ombre des Jeunes Filles en Fleurs, the second novel, you get Proust's best stuff all the time. Sudden narrative shifts toward his most beguiling characters, head snapping hilarity, eavesdropping on startling social exchanges, thrilling poetic imagery, evocative apercu, the lure of self-discovery. Plus snide comments on everyone else's use of the French language.\nIf you confined your comments to the 350 pages of flower descriptions following the Overture in Swann’s Way, okay, point taken. But out of a 3400 page work, he got most of them just right.\nMoment by moment, Proust provides miracles —\n“A little tap at the window, as though some missile had struck it, followed by a plentiful, falling sound, as light, though, as if a shower of sand were being sprinkled from a window overhead; then the fall spread, took on an order, a rhythm, became liquid, loud, drumming, musical, innumerable, universal. It was the rain.”"}
{"_id": "4c13310e", "question": "If my tortoise manages to escape from my garden, do you think he will try and come back because he lets me stroke his head?", "answers": "I don’t know how to answer this question and not come off rude.\nA tortoise doesn’t “need” us in the wild. They don’t really give a crap that we are even around while they are our pets as long as they get food and water every morning and evening. Can people have a bond with them? Yeah but not like a dog or cat - and they always run away from home for good.\nDo I think it’ll come back? Who the hell knows. Maybe? However what upsets me with this is that you KNOW the tortoise can get out and most likely will again… and instead of doing something to contain the pet you pledged to take care off… you are asking the internet if they will come back.\nMaybe fix the issue so they can’t get out and you won’t have to worry about them coming back or not?"}
{"_id": "419897cc", "question": "If I'm having a stroke and I managed to call 911, but I can't talk, will they find out where I am, and how can they know in what apartment I am in? If I'm not talking, why wouldn't they just hang up on me?", "answers": "I am often advising 911 callers: location first!!!! And there is good reason for that advice. If they cannot locate you, they cannot treat you, If you call from a landline the chances are very good that they are going to be able to know what address and apartment number the call came from. BUT if you can't speak, stay on the line anyway;Press #3 for an ambulance. If the operator asks YOU questions #4 is yes, #5 is “no” It might just take some extra time. Although I've harped upon the importance of location in the past here on quora I do understand that many if not most times you will be located, but in cases like this seconds matter.In the case of a stroke call nine-one-one and as usual follow directions the best you can and I am sure you that they will make every attempt to locate you and most likely will be successful. But remember the 3–4–5 codes mentioned, and have confidence in their training. They don't just hang up. They're training covers situations where the caller can't respond."}
{"_id": "bc4b9ef5", "question": "What is a common response for managing heat cramps, heat exhaustion, and heat stroke?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "db460475", "question": "Is endovascular cooling more efficient, and beneficial than external targeted temperature management(TTM) for brain surgeries or stroke treatment?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "6a5e6f43", "question": "How do you manage blood glucose levels after stroke for a heart patient?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "301806a6", "question": "How can the Land Rover Td5 engine management system determine correct injection timing? This 4 stroke diesel engine has a crankshaft position sensor but no camshaft position sensor, and uses unit injectors that are controlled electronically…", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "06bb6d98", "question": "In acute management of stroke, why is the usage of tissue plasminogen activators (tPA-alteplase) contra-indicated after 4.5 hours? Why can't you try it that?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "c9530ad7", "question": "What is the first line of physiotherapy management in case of a stroke patient at ICU? What are the periodical tests to be done to monitor the prognosis during physiotherapy treatment?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "e2adfd76", "question": "How do you manage cardiophobia (irrational fear of heart stroke)?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "b687e5e8", "question": "How do you manage the medical costs for your immigrant parents? My mom had a stroke, and she needs a caretaker two times a day, and dad has an Alzheimer onset.", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "89e8a8cf", "question": "Yesterday my father dad a stroke…I am away from home and unable to get a flight. I'm so afraid of losing him and not even being able to see him for the last time. It's unbelievable how my whole world is drowning and. How you manage all this pain?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "9620dc3d", "question": "Can course management help shave some strokes off your handicap? If so, how much would you pay to play with the local golf pro at your home course?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "8e9fa3bd", "question": "I recently had a brain hemorrhage and luckily have been left with no long lasting disabilities but I am struggling with stroke fatigue, any ideas how on how to manage this?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "4b72a0bf", "question": "How can I return to a part-time work? I worked at a management level at a US MNC. Three years ago, I suffered a major heart attack. After that, I suffered three strokes. Thankfully, I recovered fully.", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "30fa3dfb", "question": "As a centrist, I am really curious how Narendra Modi managed to become Prime Minister, a major political achievement, without any political legacy behind him. Is it sheer hardwork, a stroke of luck, or a planned strategy over many years?", "answers": ""}
{"_id": "73a8e336", "question": "What are the solutions on water pollution?", "answers": "A very important question, with so many aspects.\nFirst there are ditches, canals, rivers, lakes and the sea. Then are many kinds of pollution, and they can behave different. And allso there are several ways pollution ends up in the water.\nLet’s break this down. The pollution (I assume you’re talking about) comes from humans. The main sources are houses, industrial activities, transport and mining. The polution can be mineral, chemical or biologal. Humans have a habit of cleaning everything with water. In times there were no detergents and complex chemicals and there were not so many people, that was not a big deal.\nNowadays most pollution can be prevented by using less toxic substances and waste water treatment. The treatment has to be able to take out or neutralize de pollution. Biological waste (like faeces) in small amounts is no big problem, but in large amounts the rotting proces can take all the oxygen out of the water and kill all life. In the oceans this will allmost never happen, because it becomes diluted. But treatment costs money, and in many countrys this will take a huge amount of effort.\nIn countries that allready have waste water treatment there are often still many things to improve. E.g. in many countries waste-water of big areas is treated in large plants, but water from roofs is on the same sewerage-system. That can cause the treatment-plant to be flushed when there is heavy rainfall.\nTo top this all off strict legislation is needed. Important is the ban on non-biodegradable plastics, and preventing ships dumping bilge-oil and other waste in the sea.\nA difficult problem is toxicm (mineral) waste-water from mining. This is hard to take out of the water and (often) governments that share in the profit don’t give a damn."}
{"_id": "75425291", "question": "Why is sex so painful? When my boyfriend tries to insert his penis, it hurts at first and then he manages to put it in. After that, the strokes are uncomfortable and slightly painful. I suspect it’s a lube problem, but what else could it be?", "answers": "It is possible that his penis may not actually be penetrating your vagina - but basically stroking between the outer lips of vagina and the inner lips of vagina.\nIt has happened a lot initially and a few times even much later with my current partner that my penis would enter her vagina but would stroke between the outer and inner lips of her vagina— at one point when she had not been cleaning herself properly, my penis was covered with a white, curd-like discharge, which was basically the muck that had been gathering between the inner and outer lips of her vagina.\nTo ensure that you penetrate her properly ask her to finger-fuck her vagina before penetration and/or ask her to hold and guide your penis into her vagina.\nAlso, consider fucking her in short shallow strokes while letting her occassionally touch her pussy while fucking and/or touch to guide your penis if needed.\nThis happens a lot in older women who started having sex later in life and who have not yet got habituated to regular sex to the point of being able to reflexively manage the mechanics of sex to the point of being able to debug pains like this.\nHope this helps.\nBookmark this answer - since I will try to edit and add more information to this answer - both from personal experience and based on what I have read and learnt.\n-N"}
